Bayani Rafael A. Elogada

25B West Santiago St. Paltok Quezon City 1105 +63 995 567 3292 (Globe Telecom) bayanielogada@gmail.com

I am an Ateneo/UP alumnus who has a knack for tech and anything cyber-related. I have intermediate experience in systems administration and webmastering, and extensive experience in documentation and content management.

Education

BS Industrial Engineering 2010-2012 UP Diliman

High school Degree 2006-2010 Ateneo De Manila

Skills

- Linux Administration (Debian, Ubuntu, Kali)
- Firewall management Virtual Private Servers (DigitalOcean, Microsoft Azure)
- Documentation, seminar transcription, etc.
- Content-writing, Blog management
- SEO and analytics Google Analytics (Universal Analytics, Google G4)

Professional Experience

Documenter

Mediator's Network for Sustainable Peace Inc.

January 2011- January 2016

Wrote minutes and transcripts of events. Wrote written content on case studies in workshops. Wrote study material for workshop members. Provided after-action reports to the company on projects.

- > Minutes and transcription
- > Post-event reports
- > Tabulation of events
- > Used tools such as MS Office and Photoshop

Technical Support

Sitel Mandaluyong

May to August 2019

Asked users about tech-related issues. Assigned customers to proper departments (sales, complaints, etc) when needed. Updated corporate log system according to calls accrued.

- > Repairs of laptops and printers, client was Hewlett-Packard (HP)
- > Team communication with diff. departments
- > Tools included virtual machines, soft phones, remote desktop protocol
- > Logged events in company app

Bug Bounty Hunter

Bugcrowd Inc.

https://bugcrowd.com/metamudkip

March 2018- December 2020

Freelance, security researcher. Researched on software vulnerabilities in multiple webapps.. Attempted to follow the Pentesting Life Cycle to provide input on security improvements.

- > Software vulnerabilities and VAPT
- > OWASP Top 10, Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVE), NVD Database
- > Tools included Linux, cloud solutions such as MS Azure, OWASP ZAP, Nmap, etc
- > Learned professional communication with international tech teams

IT Consultant

Mediator's Network for Sustainable Peace Inc.

July 2020

Interviewed incoming tech personnel. Provided input on cloud solutions' vendors and software. Provided input on scheduling of tech personnel interviews.

- > Gave input to Board of Trustees on tech solutions
- > Made way for permanent staff, including screening and training
- > Prepared tools for staff before being hired
- > Tools used include remote desktop protocol (RDP), Skype, Google Meet

QA Intern/ DevOps Intern

Flowerstore.ph

October 2021 to January 2022

Provided timely reports on quality assurance and provided code changes via BitBucket. Made sure to follow DevOps standards when working. Also provided 1 VAPT for the company

- > Git (BitBucket)
- > PHP (Laravel) Node.js, Vue.js, Tailwind CSS
- > Learned how to do QA ticketing and bug logging
- > Provided 1 VAPT

Webmaster

http://www.listchan.com

July 2021 onwards

Managed SEO. Created content. Funneled viewer traffic via marketing affiliates. Managed analytics using Google Universal Analytics and Google Search Console. Monetized with Adsense.

- > Prepared website content
- > Bought my own domain
- > Provided cybersecurity and basic cyber forensics
- > Tools include Google Analytics, DNS utilities, Linux (Debian, Kali Linux, Ubuntu)

Certificates and Workshops CompTIA Security+ Bootcamp Fast Track IT PH 2020 Certificate available on request

References

List of references and contact details available on request